THE CAPITAL JURY PROJECT RECORDS (APAP196) 1941-2011
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- CJP Phase I, 1990-2004; 1; 30.4
  - Audiotapes of Juror Interviews, 1990-2004; 1.3
    - CA 0085*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 158)
    - CA 0085*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 159)
    - CA 0086*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 160)
    - CA 0086*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 161)
    - CA 0086*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 162)
    - CA 0086*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 163)
    - CA 0087*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 164)
    - CA 0087*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 165)
    - CA 0087*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 166)
    - CA 0087*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 167)
    - CA 0087*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 168)
    - CA 0087*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 169)
    - CA 0088*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 170)
    - CA 0088*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 171)
    - CA 0088*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 172)
    - CA 0090*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 173)
    - CA 0090*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 174)
    - CA 0090*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 175)
    - CA 0093*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 176)
    - CA 0093*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 177)
    - CA 0094*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 178)
    - CA 0094*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 179)
    - CA 0095*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 180)
    - CA 0095*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 181)
    - CA 0096*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 182)
    - CA 0096*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 183)
    - CA 0097*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 184)
    - CA 0097*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 185)
    - CA 0100*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 186)
    - CA 0100*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 187)
    - CA 0102*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 188)
    - CA 0102*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 189)
    - CA 0103*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 190)
    - CA 0103*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 191)
    - CA 0107*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 192)
    - CA 0107*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 193)
    - CA 0113*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 194)
    - CA 0113*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 195)
    - CA 0114*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 196)
    - CA 0114*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 197)
    - CA 0116*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 198)
    - CA 0116*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 199)
    - CA 0117*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 200)
    - CA 0117*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 201)
    - CA 0118*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 202)
    - CA 0118*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 203)
    - CA 0118*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 204)
    - CA 0118*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 205)
    - CA 0119*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 206)
    - CA 0119*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 207)
    - CA 0119*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 208)
    - CA 0120*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 209)
    - CA 0120*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 210)
    - CA 0120*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 211)
    - CA 0121*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 212)
    - CA 0121*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 213)
    - CA 0123*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 214)
    - CA 0123*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 215)
    - CA 0123*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 216)
    - CA 0125*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 217)
    - CA 0125*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 218)
    - CA 0125*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 219)
    - CA 0126*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 220)
    - CA 0126*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 221)
    - CA 0126*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 222)
    - CA 0126*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 223)
    - CA 0127*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 224)
    - CA 0127*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 225)
    - CA 0127*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 226)
    - CA 0128*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 227)
    - CA 0129*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 228)
    - CA 0129*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 229)
    - CA 0130*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 230)
    - CA 0130*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 231)
    - CA 0131*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 232)
    - CA 0131*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 233)
    - CA 0131*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 234)
    - CA 0131*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 235)
    - CA 0131*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 236)
    - CA 0132*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 237)
    - CA 0132*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 238)
    - CA 0134*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 239)
    - CA 0136*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 240)
    - CA 0136*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 241)
    - CA 0136*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 242)
    - CA 0137*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 243)
    - CA 0137*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 244)
    - CA 0138*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 245)
    - CA 0138*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 246)
    - CA 0140*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 247)
    - CA 0140*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 248)
    - CA 0144*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 249)
    - CA 0144*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 250)
    - CA 0145*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 251)
    - CA 0145*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 252)
    - CA 0146*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 253)
    - CA 0146*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 254)
    - CA 0146*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 255)
    - CA 0148*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 256)
    - CA 0149*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 257)
    - CA 0149*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 258)
    - CA 1951*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 259)
    - CA 1951*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 260)
    - CA 1952*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 261)
    - CA 1952*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 262)
    - CA 1952*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 263)
    - CA 1955*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 264)
    - CA 1955*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 265)
    - CA 1960*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 266)
    - CA 1960*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 267)
    - CA 1962*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 268)
    - CA 1962*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 269)
    - CA 1962*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 270)
    - FL 0152*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 271)
    - FL 0153*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 272)
    - FL 0153*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 273)
    - FL 0153*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 274)
    - FL 0155*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 275)
    - FL 0155*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 276)
    - FL 0158*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 277)
    - FL 0158*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 278)
    - FL 0159*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 279)
    - FL 0159*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 280)
    - FL 0159*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 281)
    - FL 0160*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 282)
    - FL 0160*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 283)
    - FL 0160*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 284)
    - FL 0160*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 285)
    - FL 0161*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 286)
    - FL 0161*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 287)
    - FL 0161*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 288)
    - FL 0162*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 289)
    - FL 0162*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 290)
    - FL 0162*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 291)
    - FL 0163/ FL 0164*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 292)
    - FL 0164*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 293)
    - FL 0167*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 294)
    - FL 0168*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 295)
    - FL 0168*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 296)
    - FL 0169*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 297)
    - FL 0171*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 298)
    - FL 0171*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 299)
    - FL 0171*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 300)
    - FL 0173*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 301)
    - FL 0173*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 302)
    - FL 0173*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 303)
    - FL 0174*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 304)
    - FL 0174*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 305)
    - FL 0174*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 306)
    - FL 0175*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 307)
    - FL 0175*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 308)
    - FL 0176*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 309)
    - FL 0177*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 310)
    - FL 0178*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 311)
    - FL 0179*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 312)
    - FL 0180*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 313)
    - FL 0180*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 314)
    - FL 0181*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 315)
    - FL 0183*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 316)
    - FL 0168*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 317)
    - FL 0188/ FL 0190*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 318)
    - FL 0188*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 319)
    - FL 0190*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 320)
    - FL 0191*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 321)
    - FL 0192*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 322)
    - FL 0193*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 323)
    - FL 0194*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 324)
    - FL 0195*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 325)
    - FL 0195/ FL 0197*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 326)
    - FL 0195*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 327)
    - FL 0195*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 328)
    - FL 0196*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 329)
    - FL 0196*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 330)
    - FL 0196*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 331)
    - FL 0197*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 332)
    - FL 0197*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 333)
    - FL 0197*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 334)
    - FL 0197*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 335)
    - FL 0198*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 336)
    - FL 0198*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 337)
    - FL 0203*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 338)
    - FL 0203*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 339)
    - FL 0203*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 340)
    - FL 0204*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 341)
    - FL 0204*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 342)
    - FL 0204*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 343)
    - FL 0205/ FL 0170*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 344)
    - FL 0206/ FL 0220*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 345)
    - FL 0212*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 346)
    - FL 0212*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 347)
    - FL 0215*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 348)
    - FL 0215*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 349)
    - FL 0215*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 350)
    - FL 0216*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 351)
    - FL 0216*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 352)
    - FL 0216*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 353)
    - FL 0218*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 354)
    - FL 0218*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 355)
    - FL 0218*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 356)
    - FL 0219/ FL 0222*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 357)
    - FL 0219/ FL 0222*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 358)
    - FL 0222/ FL 0219*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 359)
    - FL 0222*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 360)
    - FL 0225*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 361)
    - FL 0226*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 362)
    - FL 0227*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 363)
    - FL 0229*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 364)
    - FL 0231*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 365)
    - FL 0233*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 366)
    - FL 0234*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 367)
    - FL 0236*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 368)
    - FL 0237*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 369)
    - FL 0238*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 370)
    - FL 0240*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 371)
    - FL 0241*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 372)
    - FL 0246*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 373)
    - FL 0246*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 374)
    - FL 0246*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 375)
    - FL 0249*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 376)
    - FL 0250*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 377)
    - FL 0250*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 378)
    - FL 0250*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 379)
    - FL 0251*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 380)
    - FL 0252*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 381)
    - FL 0253*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 382)
    - FL 0254*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 383)
    - FL 0255*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 384)
    - FL 0255*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 385)
    - FL 0255*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 386)
    - FL 0256*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 387)
    - FL 0256*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 388)
    - FL 0257*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 389)
    - FL 0258*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 390)
    - FL 0258*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 391)
    - FL 0259*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 392)
    - FL 0259*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 393)
    - FL 0260*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 394)
    - FL 0261*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 395)
    - FL 0261*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 396)
    - FL 0263*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 397)
    - FL 0263*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 398)
    - FL 0263*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 399)
    - FL 0263*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 400)
    - FL 0264*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 401)
    - FL 0264*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 402)
    - FL 0264*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 403)
    - FL 0264*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 404)
    - FL 0265*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 405)
    - FL 0265*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 406)
    - FL 0265*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 407)
    - FL 0267*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 408)
    - FL 0267*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 409)
    - FL 0267*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 410)
    - FL 0267*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 411)
    - FL 0267*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 412)
    - FL 0268*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 413)
    - FL 0268*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 414)
    - FL 0269*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 415)
    - FL 0269*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 416)
    - FL 0269*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 417)
    - FL 0270*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 418)
    - FL 0270*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 419)
    - FL 0270*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 420)
    - FL 1063*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 421)
    - GA 0301*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 422)
    - GA 0301*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 423)
    - GA 0301*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 424)
    - GA 0302*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 425)
    - GA 0302*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 426)
    - GA 0302*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 427)
    - GA 0302*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 428)
    - GA 0303*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 429)
    - GA 0303*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 430)
    - GA 0303*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 431)
    - GA 0303*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 432)
    - GA 0304*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 433)
    - GA 0304*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 434)
    - GA 0305*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 435)
    - GA 0306*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 436)
    - GA 0307*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 437)
    - GA 0307*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 438)
    - GA 0307*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 439)
    - GA 0308*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 440)
    - GA 0308*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 441)
    - GA 0309*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 442)
    - GA 0309*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 443)
    - GA 0313*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 444)
    - GA 0313*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 445)
    - GA 0314*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 446)
    - GA 0314*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 447)
    - GA 0315*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 448)
    - GA 0315*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 449)
    - GA 0316*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 450)
    - GA 0328*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 451)
    - GA 0333*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 452)
    - GA 0333*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 453)
    - GA 0333*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 454)
    - GA 0333*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 455)
    - GA 0334*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 456)
    - GA 0334*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 457)
    - GA 0334*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 458)
    - GA 0335*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 459)
    - GA 0335*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 460)
    - GA 0335*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 461)
    - GA 0335*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 462)
    - GA 0336*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 463)
    - GA 0336*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 464)
    - GA 0336*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 465)
    - GA 0336*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 466)
    - GA 0336*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 467)
    - GA 0336*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 468)
    - GA 0336*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 469)
    - GA 0336*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 470)
    - GA 0336*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 471)
    - GA 0337*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 472)
    - GA 0337*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 473)
    - GA 0337*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 474)
    - GA 0337*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 475)
    - GA 0337*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 476)
    - GA 0337*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 477)
    - GA 0337*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 478)
    - GA 0338*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 479)
    - GA 0338*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 480)
    - GA 0338*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 481)
    - GA 0338*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 482)
    - GA 0338*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 483)
    - GA 0338*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 484)
    - GA 0339*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 485)
    - GA 0339 *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 486)
    - GA 0339*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 487)
    - GA 0339*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 488)
    - GA 0340*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 489)
    - GA 0340*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 490)
    - GA 0340*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 491)
    - GA 0341*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 492)
    - GA 0341*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 493)
    - GA 0341*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 494)
    - GA 0341*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 495)
    - GA 0342*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 496)
    - GA 0342*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 497)
    - GA 0342*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 498)
    - GA 0342*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 499)
    - GA 0342*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 500)
    - GA 0342*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 501)
    - GA 0345*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 502)
    - GA 0345*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 503)
    - GA 0345*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 504)
    - GA 0345*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 505)
    - GA 0346*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 506)
    - GA 0346*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 507)
    - GA 0346*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 508)
    - GA 0346*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 509)
    - GA 0349*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 510)
    - GA 0349*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 511)
    - GA 0349*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 512)
    - GA 0349*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 513)
    - GA 0349*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 514)
    - GA 0349*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 515)
    - GA 0350*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 516)
    - GA 0350*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 517)
    - GA 0350*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 518)
    - GA 0350*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 519)
    - GA 0350*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 520)
    - GA 0350*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 521)
    - GA 0351*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 522)
    - GA 0351*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 523)
    - GA 0351*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 524)
    - GA 0353*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 525)
    - GA 0353*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 526)
    - GA 0353*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 527)
    - GA 0354*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 528)
    - GA 0354*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 529)
    - GA 0355*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 530)
    - GA 0355*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 531)
    - GA 0355*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 532)
    - GA 0355*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 533)
    - GA 0356*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 534)
    - GA 0356*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 535)
    - GA 0357*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 536)
    - GA 0358*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 537)
    - GA 0359*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 538)
    - GA 0359*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 539)
    - GA 0360*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 540)
    - GA 0360*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 541)
    - GA 0360*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 542)
    - GA 0361*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 543)
    - GA 0361*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 544)
    - GA 0362*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 545)
    - GA 0362*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 546)
    - GA 0364*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 547)
    - GA 0364*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 548)
    - GA 0365*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 549)
    - GA 0365*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 550)
    - GA 0365*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 551)
    - GA 0365*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 552)
    - GA 0369*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 553)
    - GA 0369*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 554)
    - GA 0370*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 555)
    - GA 0370*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 556)
    - GA 0373*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 557)
    - GA 0373*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 558)
    - GA 0374*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 559)
    - GA 0375*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 560)
    - GA 0376*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 561)
    - GA 0376*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 562)
    - GA 0377*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 563)
    - GA 0377*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 564)
    - GA 0378*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 565)
    - GA 0378*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 566)
    - GA 0378*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 567)
    - GA 0378*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 568)
    - GA 0378*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 569)
    - GA 0378*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 570)
    - GA 0381*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 571)
    - GA 0381*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 572)
    - GA 0381*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 573)
    - GA 0382*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 574)
    - GA 0382*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 575)
    - GA 0383*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 576)
    - GA 0383*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 577)
    - GA 0383/ GA 0484*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 578)
    - GA 0384*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 579)
    - GA 0384*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 580)
    - GA 0384*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 581)
    - GA 0384*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 582)
    - GA 0384*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 583)
    - GA 0385*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 584)
    - GA 0385*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 585)
    - GA 0386*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 586)
    - GA 0386*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 587)
    - GA 0386*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 588)
    - GA 0386*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 589)
    - GA 0387*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 590)
    - GA 0387*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 591)
    - GA 0388*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 592)
    - GA 0388*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 593)
    - GA 0389*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 594)
    - GA 0389*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 595)
    - GA 0390*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 596)
    - GA 0393*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 597)
    - GA 0393*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 598)
    - GA 0393*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 599)
    - GA 0397*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 600)
    - GA 0397*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 601)
    - GA 0398*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 602)
    - GA 0398*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 603)
    - GA 0398*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 604)
    - GA 0399*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 605)
    - GA 0399*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 606)
    - GA 0401*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 607)
    - GA 0401*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 608)
    - GA 0450*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 609)
    - GA *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 610)
    - GA *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 611)
    - IN 0451*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 612)
    - IN 0451*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 613)
    - IN 0451*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 614)
    - IN 0452*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 615)
    - IN 0452*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 616)
    - IN 0453*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 617)
    - IN 0453*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 618)
    - IN 0454*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 619)
    - IN 0454*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 620)
    - IN 0455*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 621)
    - IN 0455*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 622)
    - IN 0455*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 623)
    - IN 0456*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 624)
    - IN 0456*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 625)
    - IN 0457*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 626)
    - IN 0458*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 627)
    - IN 0460*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 628)
    - IN 0460*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 629)
    - IN 0461*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 630)
    - IN 0461*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 631)
    - IN 0464*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 632)
    - IN 0464*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 633)
    - IN 0465*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 634)